{
    "id": "55553250fcf847a09ebccec199539f44",
    "title": "Since And For",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been associated with this institution …………….. ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ecb00865c25e4d40b86d3530dc275c49"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been ailing ……………… November.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b86086ca76f24e6caa1b8c1787c813ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. when have you been attending the course?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29d71549b4a04627804855dbc604f1a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "These foreigners have been learning Sanskrit ………………… six months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2b1523e9b294aa2b9c4945327739e8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister has been learning music ………………. last January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f27149020aa24f7787a511b4b80e9088"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has worked as a peon ……………. ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6329d20faf864df3b17d3ed5b29d2cc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known Kumar ……………. two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05f9d80ceb604b7f834f8f24fb845536"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known Kumar …………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f422f7b9a77454c8261713a35e71fed"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been teaching yoga …………….. three years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7af0abad52f459cb428c215a65a8773"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. when have you been learning music ?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f3254e631114709ac8f47cd192eccfa"
        }
    ]
}